Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - J
        - Unknown - I'll live 4 U, 2000; SR-18380 (Box 313)
          In same jacket as # SR-18379. Different discs. Unknown artist.
          Catalog # PRO-A-100160; A-side Matrix # PRO A 1001601 A SR1
        - Jones, Quincy - Stomp (disc one), 1995; SR-18381; Jones, Quincy (Box 313)
          In same jacket as # SR-18382. Double album.
          Catalog # PRO-A-8403; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-8403-A-SR1
        - Jones, Quincy - Stomp (disc two), 1995; SR-18382; Jones, Quincy (Box 313)
          In same jacket as # SR-18381. Double album.
          Catalog # PRO-A-8403; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-8403-C-SR1
        - Jones, Quincy - I'll be good to you, 1989; SR-18383; Jones, Quincy (Box 313)
          Catalog # 0-21408; A-side Matrix # 0-21408-A-SR1
        - Jones, Quincy - The dude, 1981; SR-18384; Jones, Quincy (Box 313)
          Catalog # SP-03721; A-side Matrix # A&MSP03721A-P1
        - Jones, Quincy - Something I cannot have, 1999; SR-18385; Jones, Quincy (Box 313)
        - Jones, Quincy - Something I cannot have, 1999; SR-18386; Jones, Quincy (Box 313)
        - Jones, Quincy - Something I cannot have, 1999; SR-18387; Jones, Quincy (Box 313)
        - Jones, Quincy - Stomp (disc one), 1995; SR-18388; Jones, Quincy (Box 313)
          In same jacket as # SR-18389. Double album.
        - Jones, Quincy - Stomp (disc two), 1995; SR-18389; Jones, Quincy (Box 313)
          In same jacket as # SR-18388. Double album.
        - Jones, Quincy - Ai no corrida (I-no-ko-ree-da), 1981; SR-18390; Jones, Quincy (Box 313)
          Catalog # SP-17143; A-side Matrix # A&MSP017143A-S1
        - Jones, Quincy - Stomp (disc one), 1995; SR-18391; Jones, Quincy (Box 313)
          In same jacket as # SR-18392. Double album.
        - Jones, Quincy - Stomp (disc two), 1995; SR-18392; Jones, Quincy (Box 313)
          In same jacket as # SR-18391. Double album.
        - Jones, Shae - Bad boy, 1999; SR-18393; Jones, Shae (Box 313)
          Catalog # U8P 1456; A-side Matrix # J8P-1456-A
        - Jones, Shae - Bad boy, 1999; SR-18394; Jones, Shae (Box 313)
        - Jones, Shae - Bad boy remixes, 1999; SR-18395; Jones, Shae (Box 313)
          Catalog # U8P 1527; A-side Matrix # U8P-1527-B
        - Jones, Shae - Talk show shhh!, 1998; SR-18396; Jones, Shae (Box 313)
          Catalog # U8P 1404; A-side Matrix # U8P-1404-A
        - Jones, Shirley - Do you get enough love, 1985; SR-18397; Jones, Shirley (Box 313)
          Catalog # SPRO-9679; A-side Matrix # SPRO-1-9679-240917A-Z1
        - Jones, Shirley - Do you get enough love, 1985; SR-18398; Jones, Shirley (Box 313)
        - Jones, Spencer - How to win your love, 1986; SR-18399; Jones, Spencer (Box 313)
          Catalog # PRO-7105; A-side Matrix # PRO-7105-A
        - Jones, Tamiko - Can't live without your love, 1979; SR-18400; Jones, Tamiko (Box 313)
          Catalog # PD D 513; A-side Matrix # PDD-5137GNP-4348-5-CP1
        - Jones, Tiki - Love gets going, 1998; SR-18401; Jones, Tiki (Box 313)
          Catalog # GG-1003; A-side Matrix # GG-1003 A
          Gossip Records
        - Jones, Tom - Tom Jones sings she's a lady, 1971; SR-18402; Jones, Tom (Box 313)
          Catalog # XPAS71046; A-side Matrix # ZAL 10599
          Parrot
        - Jones, Tom - She's a lady, 1995; SR-18403; Jones, Tom (Box 313)
          Catalog # MCA12 55144; A-side Matrix # MCA 12458 FDS-1
        - Jones, Tom - She's a lady, 1995; SR-18404; Jones, Tom (Box 313)
        - Jones, Tom - What's new pussycat?, 1965; SR-18405; Jones, Tom (Box 313)
          Catalog # PAS 71006; A-side Matrix # ZAL6911-1C
        - Joneses - Summer groove, 2014; SR-18406; Joneses (Box 313)
          Catalog # 77733; A-side Matrix # 77333-A
          Good Records
        - Joneses - Sugar pie guy, 1983; SR-18407; Joneses (Box 313)
          Catalog # 422-810 309-1; A-side Matrix # 422810309-1AS-PRC-CH
        - JonH & Raskal - Ten daze ago, 2003; SR-18408; JonH & Raskal (Box 313)
          Catalog # RMR 020; A-side Matrix # RMR020A1
          Red Menace Records
        - JonH & Raskal - Drop the beat, 2002; SR-18409; JonH & Raskal (Box 313)
          Catalog # RMR 015; A-side Matrix # RMR015A
        - JonH & Raskal - Drop the beat, 2002; SR-18410; JonH & Raskal (Box 313)
        - JonH & Raskal - Afro's revenge, 2002; SR-18411; JonH & Raskal (Box 313)
          Catalog # RMR 017; A-side Matrix # RMR 017A
        - JonH & Raskal - Afro's revenge, 2002; SR-18412; JonH & Raskal (Box 313)
        - Jonny Z - Latin swing, 1996; SR-18413; Jonny Z (Box 313)
          Catalog # QAL-645; A-side Matrix # QAL 645-A
          Pump Records
        - Jonzun Crew - We are the Jonzon Crew, 1983; SR-18414; Jonzun Crew (Box 313)
          Catalog # TB 834; A-side Matrix # TB-834-A
          Tommy Boy
        - Jonzun Crew - Pack jam (look out for the OVC), 1982; SR-18415; Jonzun Crew (Box 313)
          In same jacket as # SR-18416. 2 copies.
          Catalog # TB-826; A-side Matrix # TB-826-A
        - Jonzun Crew - Pack jam (look out for the OVC), 1982; SR-18416; Jonzun Crew (Box 313)
          In same jacket as # SR-18415. 2 copies.
        - Jonzun Crew - Lost in space, 1983; SR-18417; Jonzun Crew (Box 313)
          In same jacket as # SR-18418. 2 copies.
          Catalog # TBLP-1001; A-side Matrix # TBLP-1001-A
        - Jonzun Crew - Lost in space, 1983; SR-18418; Jonzun Crew (Box 313)
          In same jacket as # SR-18417. 2 copies.
        - Jonzun Crew - Pack jam (look out for the OVC), 1998; SR-18419; Jonzun Crew (Box 313)
          Catalog # TB 337; A-side Matrix # TB-337A
        - Jonzun Crew - Pack jam (look out for the OVC), 1998; SR-18420; Jonzun Crew (Box 313)
        - Jonzun Crew - Time is running out, 1984; SR-18421; Jonzun Crew; Jonzun, Michael (Box 313)
          Catalog # TB 845; A-side Matrix # TB-845-A-RE
        - Jonzun Crew - Lovin', 1984; SR-18422; Jonzun Crew; Jonzun, Michael (Box 313)
          Catalog # TB 850; A-side Matrix # TB-850-A-1
        - Jonzun Crew - Lovin', 1984; SR-18423; Jonzun Crew; Jonzun, Michael (Box 313)
        - Jonzun, Michael - Games people play, 1986; SR-18424; Jonzun, Michael (Box 313)
          Catalog # SP-12168; A-side Matrix # A+M-SP-012168-B-ES1
        - Jonzun Crew - Red hott mama, 1985; SR-18425; Jonzun Crew; Jonzun, Michael (Box 313)
          Catalog # SP-12140; A-side Matrix # A+M-SP-012140-A-ES1
        - Jonzun Crew - Lovin', 1984; SR-18426; Jonzun Crew; Jonzun, Michael (Box 313)
        - Joplin, Janis - Joplin in concert (disc one), 1972; SR-18427; Joplin, Janis (Box 313)
          In same jacket as # SR-18428. Double album.
          Catalog # C2X 31160; A-side Matrix # P AL 31161-1B
        - Joplin, Janis - Joplin in concert (disc two), 1972; SR-18428; Joplin, Janis (Box 313)
          In same jacket as # SR-18427. Double album.
        - Joplin, Janis - Janis Joplin's greatest hits, 1972; SR-18429; Joplin, Janis (Box 313)
          Catalog # KC 32168; A-side Matrix # P AL 32168-1AB
        - Jordan, Montell - What's on tonight, 1996; SR-18430; Jordan, Montell (Box 313)
          Catalog # 314 574 033-1; A-side Matrix # 314-574-033-A
        - Jordan, Montell - Let's ride (remix), 1998; SR-18431; Jordan, Montell; Shaunta (Box 314)
          Catalog # DMD 2476; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-88702-1-A
        - Jordan, Montell - Come home; This cold world, 2000; SR-18432; Jordan, Montell; Lord Tariq (Box 314)
          Catalog # MJ 427; A-side Matrix # MJ427-A
          The Record Co
        - Jordan, Montell - This is how we do it, 1995; SR-18433; Jordan, Montell (Box 314)
          Catalog # 422-851 469-1; A-side Matrix # 422-851-469-1-AS
          Rush Associated Labels
        - Jordan, Stanley - Chameleon, 1994; SR-18434; Jordan, Stanley (Box 314)
          Catalog # ADP-2738; A-side Matrix # ADP-2738-SA-SP1
        - Jordan, Stanley - Flying home, 1988; SR-18435; Jordan, Stanley (Box 314)
          Catalog # E1-48682; A-side Matrix # EH48682-Z2-DMM
          Emi Manhattan Records
        - Joseph, David - Let's live it up (nite people), 1983; SR-18436; Joseph, David (Box 314)
          Catalog # PRO 7806; A-side Matrix # PRO-17806-A
        - Joseph, Larry - Today, tonight, forever (remix), 1987; SR-18437; Joseph, Larry (Box 314)
          Catalog # FM62308; A-side Matrix # FMS-62308-A
        - Joseph, Margie - Ready for the night, 1984; SR-18438; Joseph, Margie (Box 314)
          Catalog # DMD 724; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-46170-5
          Cotillion
        - Joseph, Margie - Knockout, 1982; SR-18439; Joseph, Margie (Box 314)
          Catalog # 4W9 03338; A-side Matrix # 4W9-03338-AS-1F
          Houston Connection Recording Company
        - Josias, Cori - Takin' it straight, 1983; SR-18440; Josias, Cori (Box 314)
          Catalog # 0-29665; A-side Matrix # 0-29665-A-SH1
        - Journalist - Let's get up, 2000; SR-18441; Journalist (Box 314)
          Catalog # UNIR-20316-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR-20316-1A
        - Journalist - Let's get up, 2000; SR-18442; Journalist (Box 314)
        - Jovishes - Sex gunz, SR-18443; Jovishes (Box 314)
          Catalog # BEI-304-1; A-side Matrix # AR-40810-A
          Bonafide Entertainment, Inc
        - Jovonn - Turn and run away 'running', 1990; SR-18444; Jovonn (Box 314)
          Catalog # 0-21533; A-side Matrix # 0-21533-A-SR1
        - JoVonn - My angel, 2000; SR-18445; JoVonn; Kaaye (Box 314)
          Catalog # NM004; A-side Matrix # NM-004-A
          Next Moov Records
        - JoVonn - My angel, 2000; SR-18446; JoVonn; Kaaye (Box 314)
        - J.O.Y. - Fever, SR-18447; J.O.Y. (Box 314)
          In same jacket as # SR-18448. 2 copies.
          Catalog # P.A.E. 12001; A-side Matrix # PAE 12001-A
          P.A.E.
          Brussels, Belgium
        - J.O.Y. - Fever, SR-18448; J.O.Y. (Box 314)
          In same jacket as # SR-18447. 2 copies.
        - Joy - I'm leaving, 1990; SR-18449; Joy (Box 314)
          In same jacket as # SR-18450. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SYRT 15; A-side Matrix # SYRT 15 A-1U-1-2
          Swanyard Records Ltd
        - Joy - I'm leaving, 1990; SR-18450; Joy (Box 314)
          In same jacket as # SR-18449. 2 copies.
        - Joy - I need your love, 1982; SR-18451; Joy (Box 314)
          Catalog # EA 2-870; A-side Matrix # EA2-871-A
          Eastern Records
        - Joy, Sherri - My honey's hot, 1983; SR-18452; Joy, Sherri (Box 314)
          Catalog # JBF 1946; A-side Matrix # JBF 1946-A
          Pleasure Records and Tapes
          Levittown, New York
        - Joya - I like what you're doing to me, 1994; SR-18453; Joya (Box 314)
          Catalog # 31458 0877 1; A-side Matrix # 31458-087-1A-SP1
          Atlas
        - Joya - Gettin' off on you, 1995; SR-18454; Joya (Box 314)
          Catalog # 31458 1167 1; A-side Matrix # 31458 1167 1A-SP1
        - Joya - Gettin' off on you, 1995; SR-18455; Joya (Box 314)
        - Joyner, Rodney - Easy over, 1989; SR-18456; Joyner, Rodney (Box 314)
          Catalog # SN-1001; A-side Matrix # SN-1001-A
          So-New Records
          East Orange, New Jersey
        - Jr Wilson Project - Vol. 1, SR-18457; Jr Wilson Project (Box 314)
          Catalog # XL-1965; A-side Matrix # XL-1965A
          Xtra Large Records
        - Jr Wilson - Get up higher; Ghetto Nancy, SR-18458; Jr Wilson (Box 314)
          Catalog # XL-2336; A-side Matrix # XL-2336X
        - Jr Wilson - Enter my house, SR-18459; Jr Wilson (Box 314)
          Catalog # XL-1234; A-side Matrix # XL-1234A
        - J.Rocc - Ain't no thang; Say ho!, 2004; SR-18460; J.Rocc; Steinski (Box 314)
          Catalog # STH2091; A-side Matrix # STH-2091-SA
          Stones Throw Records
        - JT Money - Superb**ch, 2001; SR-19501; JT Money (Box 314)
          Catalog # SPRO-81502; A-side Matrix # S-46541
        - JT Money - Something 'bout pimpin'; Playa ass s***, 1999; SR-19502; JT Money (Box 314)
          Catalog # 08724 81279 11; A-side Matrix # 81729-11-A
        - JT Money - Alright, 1999; SR-19503; JT Money (Box 314)
          Catalog # SPRO 81209; A-side Matrix # 81209 A
        - JT the Bigga Figga - Put yo mack hand down; Dwellin' in the labb, 1995; SR-19504; JT the Bigga Figga (Box 314)
          Catalog # SPRO 50908; A-side Matrix # SPRO 50908-A
        - JT the Bigga Figga - The mack hand (radio remix), 1995; SR-19505; JT the Bigga Figga (Box 314)
          Catalog # SPRO 30013; A-side Matrix # SPRO-30013-A
        - Jtaravhonty - Deception; Attitude, 1986; SR-19506; Jtaravhonty (Box 314)
          Catalog # SR-664; A-side Matrix # SR-664-A
          Satellite Records
        - Jtaravhonty - Deception; Attitude, 1986; SR-19507; Jtaravhonty (Box 314)
        - Ju, Trife - First night; Dangerous go-go remix, 2002; SR-19508; Ju, Trife (Box 314)
          Catalog # CR53561; A-side Matrix # CR53561-A
          Crypto Records
        - Juan-Mil - I ain't playin'; It's my year, 2004; SR-19509; Juan-Mil (Box 314)
          No entry in Discogs.
          Catalog # REBP-0001; A-side Matrix # 9576-RR001
          Rebel Records
        - Juice - Rock your body down, 1984; SR-19510; Juice (Box 314)
          Catalog # ED 4959; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-66971-A-25
        - Juicy - I've got something, 1982; SR-19511; Juicy (Box 314)
          Catalog # SP 125; A-side Matrix # SP-125-SA-CT6
        - Juicy - Beat street strut, 1984; SR-19512; Juicy (Box 314)
          Catalog # DMD 742; A-side Matrix # ST DM 46361-2
        - Julio - Guajira; Oye como va, 1994; SR-19513; Julio; Iglesias, Julio (Box 314)
          Catalog # CAS 6420; A-side Matrix # XSS6420A-1A
        - Julio - Wanksta's paradox, 1996; SR-19514; Julio (Box 314)
          Catalog # YOY; A-side Matrix # B003-A YOY
          Yaw Mama's Bichass
        - Julius, Orlando - Orlando's afro ideas 1969-72 (disc one), 2003; SR-19515; Julius, Orlando; Orlando Julius & His Afro Sounders (Box 314)
          In same jacket as # SR-19516. Double album.
          Catalog # EKOSNDLP001; A-side Matrix # EKOSNDLP001 A-1
          Ekosound
        - Julius, Orlando - Orlando's afro ideas 1969-72 (disc two), 2003; SR-19516; Julius, Orlando; Orlando Julius & His Afro Sounders (Box 314)
          In same jacket as # SR-19515. Double album.
        - Jumpin' Joe & His Revue - Jumpi' Joe & His Revue, SR-19517; Jumpin' Joe & His Revue (Box 314)
          Catalog # SR-9301; A-side Matrix # SR-9301-A
          Sensational Records
        - Jungle Band - Jungle Groove, 1988; SR-19518; Jungle Band (Box 314)
          Catalog # CRB1197; A-side Matrix # CRB 1197 A
          Charly Groove
        - Jungle Brothers - Ultimatum ultamatrix; Jungle beats; Jungle bass, 1988; SR-19519; Jungle Brothers (Box 314)
          Catalog # GEE 12005; A-side Matrix # GEE-12005-A-1
          Gee Street
        - Jungle Brothers - How ya want it (I got it), 1996; SR-19520; Jungle Brothers (Box 314)
          Catalog # PR12 7313-1; A-side Matrix # PR12-7313-1ASP
        - Jungle Brothers - Beyond this world; Promo No. 2, 1989; SR-19521; Jungle Brothers (Box 314)
          In same jacket as # SR-19522. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 0-21390; A-side Matrix # 021390A
        - Jungle Brothers - Beyond this world; Promo No. 2, 1989; SR-19522; Jungle Brothers (Box 314)
          In same jacket as # SR-19521. 2 copies.
        - Jungle Brothers - Doin' our own dang, 1989; SR-19523; Jungle Brothers (Box 314)
          Catalog # 0-21728; A-side Matrix # 0-21728-A-SR1
        - Jungle Brothers - On the run, 1988; SR-19524; Jungle Brothers (Box 314)
          In same jacket as # SR-19525. 2 copies.
          Catalog # WAR-022; A-side Matrix # WAR-022 A (NEW-MIX)
          Idlers Records
        - Jungle Brothers - On the run, 1988; SR-19525; Jungle Brothers (Box 314)
          In same jacket as # SR-19524. 2 copies.
        - Jungle Brothers - Because I got it like that, 1988; SR-19526; Jungle Brothers (Box 314)
          In same jacket as # SR-19527. 2 copies.
          Catalog # WAR 016; A-side Matrix # WAR 016-A
        - Jungle Brothers - Because I got it like that, 1988; SR-19527; Jungle Brothers (Box 314)
          In same jacket as # SR-19526. 2 copies.
        - Jungle Brothers - What "U" waitin' "4"?, 1989; SR-19528; Jungle Brothers (Box 315)
          Catalog # 0-21553; A-side Matrix # 0-21553-1A SR1
        - Jungle Brothers - Jungle Brothers, 1997; SR-19529; Jungle Brothers (Box 315)
          Catalog # GVAB-33504-1; A-side Matrix # GVAB-33504-1-A
        - Jungle Brothers - Jungle Brothers, 1997; SR-19530; Jungle Brothers (Box 315)
        - Jungle Brothers - Jungle Brothers, 1997; SR-19531; Jungle Brothers (Box 315)
        - Jungle Brothers - Brain, 1997; SR-19532; Jungle Brothers (Box 315)
          Catalog # PR12-G97-001; A-side Matrix # PR12-697-001-1B
        - Jungle Brothers - V.I.P., 1999; SR-19533; Jungle Brothers (Box 315)
          In same jacket as # SR19534. Double album.
          Catalog # GEE1008291; A-side Matrix # GEE 1008291 A-01-01-1
        - Jungle Brothers - V.I.P., 1999; SR-19534; Jungle Brothers (Box 315)
          In same jacket as # SR19533. Double album.
          Catalog # GEE1008291; A-side Matrix # GEE 1008291 C-01-01-1
        - Jungle Brothers - V.I.P., 1999; SR-19535; Jungle Brothers (Box 315)
          In same jacket as # SR-19536. Double album.
          Catalog # 63881-33565-1; A-side Matrix # 63881-33564 A
        - Jungle Brothers - V.I.P., 1999; SR-19536; Jungle Brothers (Box 315)
          In same jacket as # SR-19535. Double album.
          Catalog # 63881-33565-1; A-side Matrix # 63881-33564-1-C
        - Jungle Brothers - Freakin' you, 2000; SR-19537; Jungle Brothers (Box 315)
          Catalog # GVWH-33589-1; A-side Matrix # 63881-33589AWALLY
        - Jungle Brothers - Freakin' you, 2000; SR-19538; Jungle Brothers (Box 315)
        - Jungle Brothers - Because I got it like that, 1988; SR-19539; Jungle Brothers (Box 315)
        - Jungle Brothers - How ya want it, 1996; SR-19540; Jungle Brothers (Box 315)
          In same jacket as # SR-19541. Different discs.
          Catalog # PR12 7382-1; A-side Matrix # PR12-7382-1A-SP1
        - PM Dawn - Downtown Venus, 1995; SR-19541; PM Dawn (Box 315)
          In same jacket as # SR-19540. Different discs.
          Catalog # GEETDJ 63; A-side Matrix # GEET-DJ-63-A
        - Jungle Kings - Jungle Kings, 1990; SR-19542; Jungle Kings (Box 315)
          Catalog # 613 1 42; A-side Matrix # 850 613142 *A* 1
          Ariola
          Spain
        - Juni G. - Mama used to say, 1987; SR-19543; Juni G. (Box 315)
          Catalog # SQ 87511; A-side Matrix # SQM87511 A
          Esquire Records
        - Junie - Bread alone, 1980; SR-19544; Junie (Box 315)
          Catalog # NJC 36585; A-side Matrix # D AL 36585-1A
        - Junie - Bread alone, 1980; SR-19545; Junie (Box 315)
        - Junie - Rappin about rappin (uh-uh-uh); Victim of love, 1981; SR-19546; Junie (Box 315)
          Catalog # AS 933; A-side Matrix # XSS 168513-1A
        - Junie - Rappin about rappin (uh-uh-uh); Victim of love, 1981; SR-19547; Junie (Box 315)
        - Junior - Too late, 1982; SR-19548; Junior (Box 315)
          Catalog # MK 197; A-side Matrix # MK-197-56834-PRC-C1-1
        - Junior - Mama used to say, 1981; SR-19549; Junior (Box 315)
          Catalog # MDS 4014; A-side Matrix # MDS-4014-AS-PRC-C1-1
        - Junior - I can't help it, 1982; SR-19550; Junior (Box 315)
          In same jacket as # SR-19551. 2 copies.
          Catalog # MDS-4022; A-side Matrix # MDS-4022-2-56832-HRM1
        - Junior - I can't help it, 1982; SR-19551; Junior (Box 315)
          In same jacket as # SR-19550. 2 copies.
        - Junior - I can't help it, 1982; SR-19552; Junior (Box 315)
          In same jacket as # SR-19553. 2 copies.
          Catalog # MDS-4022; A-side Matrix # MDS-4022-2-56832-PRC-C-2-1
        - Junior - I can't help it, 1982; SR-19553; Junior (Box 315)
          In same jacket as # SR-19552. 2 copies.
        - Junior - Unison, 1983; SR-19554; Junior (Box 315)
          Catalog # 814 725-1; A-side Matrix # 83CS708-A-PRC-C1-1
          Casablanca
        - Junior C. Reaction - Better must come, 1986; SR-19555; Junior C. Reaction (Box 315)
          Catalog # COOLX 120; A-side Matrix # COOLX 120 A
        - Junior M.A.F.I.A. - Conspiracy, 1995; SR-19556; Junior M.A.F.I.A. (Box 315)
          In same jacket as # SR-19557. Different discs.
          Catalog # 92614-1; A-side Matrix # STBB 950355 B-1
          Big Beat
        - Junior M.A.F.I.A. - Gettin' money (the get money remix), 1996; SR-19557; Junior M.A.F.I.A. (Box 315)
          In same jacket as # SR-19556. Different discs.
          Catalog # DMD 2293; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-82975-82976-78869-1
        - Junior O. - Have fun, SR-19558; Junior O. (Box 315)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # GG-1016
          Red Bank, New Jersey
        - Junior O. - Have fun, SR-19559; Junior O. (Box 315)
        - Junior O. - Have fun, SR-19560; Junior O. (Box 315)
        - Junior Senior - Shake your coconuts, 2003; SR-19561; Junior Senior (Box 315)
          Catalog # 88281-0; A-side Matrix # ST-A-88281-B-1
        - Junk Yard - The beginning; The end EP, 1999; SR-19562; Junk Yard (Box 315)
          Catalog # JY2060-1; A-side Matrix # JY-2060-1-A
          Street Records & Tapes
        - Junkyard Band - The wood; Sardines, 1986; SR-19563; Junkyard Band (Box 315)
          Catalog # 44-05922; A-side Matrix # XSS-175241-1B
        - Junkyard Band - The wood; Sardines, 1986; SR-19564; Junkyard Band (Box 315)
        - Junkyard Band - The rippa medley; ha ha, yuck yuck yuck yah, 1995; SR-19565; Junkyard Band (Box 315)
          In same jacket as # SR-19566. 2 copies.
          Catalog # JY 2032; A-side Matrix # NR-19885A
          Street Records
        - Junkyard Band - The rippa medley; ha ha, yuck yuck yuck yah, 1995; SR-19566; Junkyard Band (Box 315)
          In same jacket as # SR-19565. 2 copies.
        - La Junta - La who?, 2002; SR-19567; La Junta (Box 315)
          Catalog # PH101; A-side Matrix # PH101-A
          Phat Trax
        - Jupitor, Jamie - Computer power, 1985; SR-19568; Jupitor, Jamie (Box 315)
          Catalog # DMSR-00666; A-side Matrix # DMSR-00666-A
          Egyptian Empire Records
        - Jurassic 5 - Quality control (instrumentals) (disc one), 2000; SR-19569; Jurassic 5 (Box 315)
          In same jacket as # SR-19570. Double album.
          Catalog # RWK-1183; A-side Matrix # RWK-1183A
          Rawkus
        - Jurassic 5 - Quality control (instrumentals) (disc two), 2000; SR-19570; Jurassic 5 (Box 315)
          In same jacket as # SR-19569. Double album.
        - Jurassic 5 - Quality control, 2000; SR-19571; Jurassic 5 (Box 315)
          Catalog # 694973301; A-side Matrix # 69493301
          Interscope Records
        - Juryman - 3, 1996; SR-19572; Juryman (Box 315)
          Catalog # NTONE 16; A-side Matrix # NTONE 16 A1
          Ntone
        - Jus Jase - Guns from Paris 2K2; What happened to the best, SR-19573; Jus Jase (Box 315)
          Catalog # BDS-959; A-side Matrix # BD-959-A
          BUDS Distribution
        - Jus Jase - Top gallist, SR-19574; Jus Jase (Box 315)
          In same jacket as # SR-19575. 2 copies.
          Catalog # BDS-956; A-side Matrix # BDS-956-A
        - Jus Jase - Top gallist, SR-19575; Jus Jase (Box 315)
          In same jacket as # SR-19574. 2 copies.
        - Just Four - We ain't, 1987; SR-19576; Just Four (Box 315)
          Catalog # DMD 1018; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-51175-51174-1
        - Just-Ice - Masterpiece, 1990; SR-19577; Just-Ice (Box 315)
          Catalog # LPRE-82016; A-side Matrix # LPRE-82016-Y
          Fresh Records
        - Just-Ice - Girls n guns, 1993; SR-19578; Just-Ice (Box 315)
          Catalog # SADJ-50037-1; A-side Matrix # 74785-5007-1-A
          Savage Records